Jon-Morgan Cobb

Phone: (805) 717-8293 | Email: jonmorgan.cobb@gmail.com
LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/feed/?trk=onboarding-landing

Github: http://github.com/Jonmorgan12

Professional Summary

Full stack web developer for hire out of Full Stack Academy, with over 8+ years of extensive customer service and face to face experience. Seeking a position that will combine software development along with critical thinking skills. Willing and eager to learn new teachings and technologies on the job!

Technical Skills

Proficient: React.js, JavaScript, JQuery, Express.js, Node.js, SQL, CSS, HTML5, JSX, Github, Git

Some Experience: Bootstrap 4, React-Bootstrap, Axios, Heroku, Netlify

Beginning: TypeScript, Angular, Vue.js, SASS,

Projects

- 1. **Virtual Traders** *Group Development* https://virtual-trader.herokuapp.com
 Full stack web app created for individuals to purchase vintage trading cards and sports memorabilia.
- 2. **Fitness Tracker** *Sole Developer* https://boring-wright-f10ed1.netlify.app Full stack web app created to track and input an individual's full workout.
- 3. **Strangers Things** *Sole Developer* https://compassionate-bartik-a21014.netlify.app Full stack web app created for individuals to sell and message others for items.

Work Experience

Freelance UI/UX Development — Self-employed

2020 - PRESENT

- Developed and designed the front end framework for local businesses based on deadlines and clients requests.
- Designed sites for professional business owners in real estate, fitness, and hospitality industries.
- Ability to problem solve and implement corrective action within a timely manner.

Strength Coach, San Luis Obispo, CA — Self-employed

2017 - PRESENT

- Aided in the UI/UX development of the official business website.
- Worked with a number of individuals with various athletic and demographic backgrounds.
- Created custom based workout plans conforming to the individual goals for long term progression.
- Built a professional relationship with my clients.

Lead-Bartender, Custom House, Avila Beach, CA

2018 - 2020

- Memorized restaurant's menu and spirits, able to answer questions about menu items, making recommendations upon request.
- Multi Tasking, Mixologist, Alcohol / Money Handling, Surplus of customer experience in stressful situations.
- Worked with a team of up to 30 individuals in a given day to all meet customers needs and satisfactions.

Education

Full Stack Academy / California Polytechnic State University, San Luis Obispo, CA — Certificate of Completion may 2020 - December 2020

Cuesta College, San Luis Obispo, CA — Coursework in Human Biology